MOSTAFA SALEH

9 Tanta, Al-Gharbia, Egypt · 01140855227

Most.saleh@hotmail.com · mostafasaleh5 · eng-mostafasaleh.blogspot.com

Senior student at the Higher Institute of Engineering and Technology KFS, with some experience with some experience in web development, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C++, desktop development with C#, the basics of SQL Server DBMS, the basics of Data Structures with C++, OOP with C# and basics of networking.

EXPERIENCE

JUL 2021 - AUG 2021

INTERN, WE

I was a trainee at Telecom Egypt Miami Exchange in Alexandria, Egypt. I learned about Introduction to Optical fibre cables, Introduction to "FTTH" networks, introduction to traffic devices such as PCM, WDH, SDH and WDM.

AUG 2021 - OCT 2021

SCHOLARSHIP HOLDER, EGFWD

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.JS and the DOM.

NOV 2022- DEC 2022

PROJECT, AIOT

Project: Pathological phenomena for broilers. I worked on the dataset to train a model to recognize sick broilers using deep learning and computer vision. The AI detects broilers and track them using and differentiate among sick and healthy broilers.

EDUCATION

4TH YEAR, SENIOR STUDENT

STUDENT, HIGHER INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY KFS

I'm a student in the fourth year Computer and Control engineering department.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, node.js
- Version Control (Git, GitHub)
- Windows and basic knowledge with Linux terminal
- RISC-V computer architecture basics

- Programming (C++, C#), basics of OOP and basics data structures
- Basic networking
- Basics of SQL server

ACTIVITIES

- I'm passionate about programming, especially lower-level programming and security, self-studying, self-development and learning new things.
- Volunteer at Momenta Team and at Coursera Translation team (15,000 words)
- Advanced English, A1 Russian and A1 German Languages
- I'm also passionate about Gymnastics especially lifting weights.